Hi, I'm sorry, but sorry, I don't know what happened. There was like an error in the
Video so I had like some kind of like battery warning. I don't know what I have a battery, but how are you guys doing?
Okay, wow
Yeah, um you see
How are you? Let me see
Hi everybody, I saw I had a pretty good good group over there, too
I was like, damn it. I think that's like my biggest premiere and like
That was interesting night last night though, I mean
He was like, I wish I could
Trust you know, I was kind of dumb to leave stroke off and Ziggy alone. I guess like I
Don't know if they're like into
You know copulating with with chickens or what I don't know what the fuck they're talking about
I mean, it's like wow
at least for like five five minutes
This is in very nice
Okay, I'm fixing the video. Thank you double dick down. Oh my gosh, who's that?
Hi gay whore
Who's that Shannon? I don't I don't know
Hi, Jamie. Linkpro, bro. Okay, here we go. We got something for you.
Do it live. Here. And I'll be able to premiere the, you know, I guess I'll premiere the video
on the show. I'm fixing it. How's it doing? How's it being fixed? Oh, I need to start it.
She might be ready. Okay, but let's see. Oh, no, hold on. It's not worth it. Hold on.
Oh, hi, SVP. This is little load me. How are you? I'm great. How are you? I'm doing great.
I actually wanted to tell you that I might be leaving Canada soon. Oh, really? Yeah, I'm tired
Well, isn't it like what isn't there free health care and like yeah, but they take so long to see people and it's not even worth it
Honestly, we're gonna move to I'm thinking somewhere in a galley. Oh, no. I mean, oh good. Oh good
Hey, where abouts?
I'm somewhere around the OC
a little like closer to the 30 minutes away from there okay closer to you closer
to me yeah yeah but I want to be 30 40 minutes away from OC so I think that
takes me to you right yeah I want to be next to you you do
I think you like me very much. You don't say very nice things, but you I don't I don't I want to I just want to be close to you
So I can knock the door and tell you
Psyche, I'm gonna take a break. Oh, no
Yeah, that's what I want to do. Actually, okay
Because how many of we've been on a lot of breaks lately like a lot like it's a lot for me
Yeah, and it's needed. It really is needed from you psyche. You're just a whole different specimen of a man
Well, I thought like you know you said you said I heard on beat us. You said that you said that
You know, I'm just a big I'm just looking for attention and stuff
So you're gonna stop doing those shorts of me, but then you posted more
Yeah, I stopped doing shorts, so now I do longer videos.
Oh, okay. Oh, oh, oh, oh, just short to yourself.
Oh, so we don't have to do longer video. Okay, yeah.
Correct. Yes.
Well, that's technically true.
That is technically true, right?
Yeah, technically.
All right, then.
I want to get closer to you and I want to start harassing you more.
Oh, no.
Yeah, I want to be your worst nightmare.
Oh, that's delightful. Thank you.
You're welcome. Hold on a second.
I mean, I'm a mod. I have mods to give away right now.
Are you a mod here, Sweet Pea?
I will be. As soon as I get a hold of your laptop,
I'm going to take control of your channel and do whatever the hell I want.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I'll turn but you can call me sweet nightmare sweet nightmare. Yeah
Okay, that makes that makes more sense than sweet pee
Okay here. Oh, oh, hey, what's up? I'll be your jiggaboo a jiggaboo. Oh my god. I think that's a racist term. Oh
I'll be your huckaboo, but that's what I meant. I'm sorry
There you go
I'll be your Huckaberry, that's what I meant to say.
Huckleberry, Huckaboo, Huckaberry, what, a honey boo boo?
Huckaboo.
Whatever, whatever it is.
Oh my gosh, you sound like a man now.
I just have a little cold.
That's why I will be taking a break from all of this.
Oh, OK.
Well, I do wish you the best.
I do wish you the best.
Thank you.
Hey Sam, what's up Noble?
Hey Noble, Jamie Noble, I remember him.
That's from wrestling, Jamie Noble.
Hey, we have another guest.
Oh no, I think I have an idea.
Are you, this doesn't look like a real person though.
All right, hold on.
I gotta get ready to leave,
if this is who I think it is.
Oh yeah, here.
Hello?
Oh my God.
Is that a guinea pig?
What is this?
It's Dominic.
Yeah, watch out psyche watch out
So you can you force ring yourself just in case no, no, he's Hebrew. I know who it is
We're not gonna lose this classic episode. He's quiet though
Okay, he's hugging his guinea pig. He's mumbling. Well, who is this?
What are you talking about? I ain't mumbling shit. Hey, fuck you fuck you
I don't talk to me like that. I'm sweet P
God I
What the hell is wrong with this guy?
I don't know.
Look at his...
Are those ray bands he's wearing?
Nah, I'm always in a good mood.
You're just fucking pissing me off.
How does he have the whole photo taking up his screen?
This guy's a doctor.
Watch out.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Oh!
Oh, I'm a doctor!
Oh my God!
Hey, I don't like the vibe this guy's doing.
Man, you're way too sketched out, bitch.
Stop tripping and kicking things.
Hey!
So it's all gravy, baby. Don't trip potato chip kids back. Relax. We're gonna have a good team
Well, what a little scumbag this guy is what yeah, I said the fucking piece of shit
Hey
No